Finding Aid for the Terrence O'Flaherty Papers PASC.0026
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1950s-2000
  - Cards K-S, (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 317)
    From Gladys Knight and the Pips, Jack Lalanne, Liberace, Arthur Murray, Jim Nabors, Bob and Ruth Newhall, Ronald and Nancy Reagan, Telly Savalas, William Shatner, Red Skelton, Barbara Stanwyck, and others.
  - Cards T-Z, (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 318)
    From Danny Thomas, Marlo Thomas, Lawrence Welk, Adam West, Robert Young, and others.
  - Cards and notes from unspecified senders, (undated) (Box 315, Folder 22)
  - Cards from businesses and other organizations (1 of 2), (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Cards from businesses and other organizations (2 of 2), (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Cards from Dennis the Menace staff and Hank Ketchum, (undated) (Box 318)
    .
  - Cards from family, (ca. 1975) (Box 315, Folder 23)
    Appears to be from family members of O'Flaherty and Charles Pfister.
  - Cards from television networks, shows, studios, and production companies (1 of 2), (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 319, Folder 1)
    ABC, HBO, KRON-TV, NBC, PBS, and others.
  - Cards from television networks, shows, studios, and production companies (2 of 2), (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 319, Folder 2)
    KQED, KPIX-5, CBS, Warner Brothers, Viacom, Krofft Productions, Donahue, and others.
  - Cards identified by sender's first name, (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 318)
  - Coglan Mail, (1983) (Box 307, Folder 7)
    Reader letters in response to O'Flaherty's column about Russ Coughlan.
  - Correspondence, (ca. 1950s - 2000s) (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and reader letters, (1974, 1978) (Box 307, Folder 10)
  - Empty envelopes, (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 315, Folder 24)
  - Ephemera (found with greeting cards), (1979, 1983) (Box 315, Folder 21)
    California Horse Racing Association pass, 1979 pocket calendar, invitation to screening of The Fighter.
  - Interesting Mail 1975, (ca. 1974-75) (Box 307, Folder 9)
    Clippings, correspondence, press releases, and reader letters.
  - Local news column mail response, (1983) (Box 307, Folder 6)
    Clippings and reader letters.
  - New Yorker (The) magazine and letter, (1972 May 2) (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - Reader Mail 1959 (Box 307, Folder 8)
  - San Francisco's Hundred Leaders of Tomorrow program and related correspondence, (1953) (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - Walt Disney Productions cards, (ca. 1960-1980) (Box 318)
- Stills, (1952-1990)
  The bulk of the series are black and white television stills, many with caption sheets providing program/series titles, names of performer(s), air date, and occasionally a brief summary of the program or scene depicted. Included are a combination of scene shots of broadcasts, rehearsal shots, publicity stills of individuals and cast members. Additionally, there are stills of music and dance programs aired on television, photographs of sports figures, politicians, and other community and public leaders, and a host of famous and infamous individuals from American social and pop-cultural life.
  The series is arranged both chronologically and alphabetically.
  - Date range 1952 (Box 1)
  - Date range 1958 (Box 1)
  - Date range 1958 (Box 2)
  - Date range 1959 (Box 2)
  - Date range 1960 (Box 3)
  - Date range 1960 (Box 4)
  - Date range 1960 (Box 5)
  - Date range 1961 (Box 4)
  - Date range 1962 (Box 3)
  - Date range 1962 (Box 4)
  - Date range 1962 (Box 5)
  - Date range 1963 (Box 5)
  - Date range 1963 (Box 6)
  - Date range 1963 (Box 7)
  - Date range 1964 (Box 5)
  - Date range 1964 (Box 6)
  - Date range 1965 (Box 7)
  - Date range 1965 (Box 8)
  - Date range 1965 (Box 10)
  - Date range 1966 (Box 9)
  - Date range 1966 (Box 11)
  - Date range 1966 (Box 12)
  - Date range 1966 (Box 13)
  - Date range 1966 (Box 14)
  - Date range 1967 (Box 10)
  - Date range 1967 (Box 15)
  - Date range 1967 (Box 16)
  - Date range 1967 (Box 17)
  - Date range 1968 (Box 15)
  - Date range 1968 (Box 16)
  - Date range 1968 (Box 17)
  - Date range 1969 (Box 17)
  - Date range 1969 (Box 18)
  - Date range 1970 (Box 19)
  - Date range 1970 (Box 20)
  - Date range 1970 (Box 21)
  - Date range 1971 (Box 21)
  - Date range 1971 (Box 22)
  - Date range 1971 (Box 23)
  - Date range 1971 (Box 62)
  - Date range 1972 (Box 24)
  - Date range 1972 (Box 25)
  - Date range 1972 (Box 26)
  - Date range 1972 (Box 27)
  - Date range 1973 (Box 28)
  - Date range 1973 (Box 29)
  - Date range 1973 (Box 30)
  - Date range 1973 (Box 31)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 32)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 33)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 34)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 35)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 35)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 36)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 37)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 38)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 38)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 39)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 40)
  - Date range 1974 (Box 41)
  - Date range 1975 (Box 41)
  - Date range 1975 (Box 42)
  - Date range 1975 (Box 43)
  - Date range 1975 (Box 44)
  - Date range 1975 (Box 44)
  - Date range 1975 (Box 45)
  - Date range 1976 (Box 46)
  - Date range 1976 (Box 47)
  - Date range 1976 (Box 48)
  - Date range 1976 (Box 49)
  - Date range 1976 (Box 49)
  - Date range 1976 (Box 50)
  - Date range 1976 (Box 51)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 52)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 53)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 54)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 55)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 56)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 57)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 58)
  - Date range 1977 (Box 59)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 60)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 61)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 62)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 63)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 64)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 65)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 66)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 66)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 67)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 68)
  - Date range 1978 (Box 69)
  - Date range 1979 (Box 69)
  - Date range 1979 (Box 70)
  - Date range 1979 (Box 71)
  - Date range 1979 (Box 71)
  - Date range 1979 (Box 72)
  - Date range 1979 (Box 73)
  - Date range 1979 (Box 74)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 75)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 76)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 77)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 77)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 78)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 79)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 80)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 80)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 81)
  - Date range 1980 (Box 82)
  - Date range 1981 (Box 83)
  - Date range 1981 (Box 84)
  - Date range 1981 (Box 85)
  - Date range 1981 (Box 86)
  - Date range 1982 (Box 86)
  - Date range 1982 (Box 87)
  - Date range 1982 (Box 88)
  - Date range 1983 (Box 89)
  - Date range 1983 (Box 90)
  - Date range 1983 (Box 91)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 92)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 93)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 94)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 95)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 96)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 97)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 97)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 98)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 99)
  - Date range 1984 (Box 100)
  - Date range 1985 (Box 101)
  - Date range 1985 (Box 102)
  - Date range 1985 (Box 103)
  - Date range 1985 (Box 104)
  - Date range 1986 (Box 101)
  - Date range 1986 (Box 102)
  - Date range 1986 (Box 103)
  - Date range 1986 (Box 104)
  - ABC headshots, (1989) (Box 329, Folder 10)
  - ABC stills, (1987 Sep 27) (Box 305, Folder 21)
    Full House, Funny You Don't Look 200, Growing Pains, Hotel, Spenser for Hire, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Dec) (Box 305, Folder 19)
    ABC Mystery Movie, ABC Sports, China Beach, A Fine Romance, Taking a Stand.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Feb 16) (Box 305, Folder 16)
    Perfect Strangers, Supercarrier, The Wonder Years, and 14 Going on 30.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Jan 26) (Box 305, Folder 17)
    Home, MacGuyver, One Life to Live, and the Winter Olympics.
  - ABC stills, (1987 Aug-Sep) (Box 321, Folder 1)
    Ohara, Proud Men, Sledge Hammer!, and Spenser: For Hire.
  - ABC stills, (1974 May-Sep) (Box 328, Folder 8)
    Nakia and Kung Fu.
  - ABC stills, (1978 Aug-Dec) (Box 328, Folder 9)
  - ABC stills, (1986 Aug) (Box 328, Folder 10)
    Bluffing It and Dolly.
  - ABC stills, (1987) (Box 328, Folder 11)
  - ABC stills, (1987 Apr-May) (Box 328, Folder 12)
    AFI Salute to Barbara Stanwyck, Superstars and their Moms, Queenie, When the Time Comes and World News This Morning.
  - ABC stills, (1987 July-Aug) (Box 328, Folder 14)
    Animal Crackups, Between Two Women, and Special Olympics.
  - ABC stills, (1987 June) (Box 328, Folder 13)
    Consenting Adult and Loving.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Oct-Nov) (Box 328, Folder 16)
    Free to Be a Family, Heartbeat, Ice Capades, Incredible Sunday, Lady Mobster, My First Love, New Years' Rockin' Eve, Monday Night Football, Roots: The Gift, Ryan White Story, and World News This Morning.
  - ABC stills, (1989) (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - ABC stills, (1989) (Box 329, Folder 2)
    ABC News, American Comedy Awards, Choices, Everybody's Baby, Father Dowling Mysteries, Galdiator, Have Faith, I Love You Perfect, International Rock Awards, Koppel Report, Jekyll and Hyde, Lori's Awesome Cookies, Love With a Twist, Mick and Frankie, etc.
  - ABC stills, (1989 Feb-May) (Box 329, Folder 5)
    Deadly Silence, Loving, and Robert Guillaume Show.
  - ABC stills, (1989 Jan) (Box 329, Folder 3)
    A Man Called Hawk, Moonlighting, Passion and Paradise, and Studio 5B.
  - ABC stills, (1989 Jan-Feb) (Box 329, Folder 4)
    61st Academy Awards, 75th Anniversary of Beverly Hills, College Basketball, Debbie Allen Special, Get Smart Again!, Just Tipsy Honey, Passion and Paradise, The Penthouse, and The Women of Brewster Place.
  - ABC stills, (1989 May) (Box 329, Folder 6)
  - ABC stills, (1989 Oct-Nov) (Box 329, Folder 9)
    Blind Witness, Hall of Fame Tip-Off Classic, and A Town's Revenge.
  - ABC stills, (1989 Sep) (Box 329, Folder 8)
    Liberace and Losing a Sister.
  - ABC stills, (1989 Sep-Dec) (Box 329, Folder 7)
    Christine Cromwell, Julie and Carol, Kojak, Monday Night Football, My Brothers' Wife, Rock Hudson, and Small Sacrifices.
  - ABC stills, (1990) (Box 329, Folder 11)
    Anything to Survive, Indianapolis 500, Into the Night, Kojak, Professional Bowlers' Tour, Ryan White Story, and Voices Within: The Story of Truddi Chase.
  - ABC stills, (1990 Feb-Apr) (Box 329, Folder 12)
    Academy Awards, Anything for Laughs, Burning Bridges, Challenger, College Basketball, Dangerous Passion, Daughter of the Streets, and Over the Limit.
  - ABC stills, (1990 Feb-Apr) (Box 329, Folder 13)
    Golf, H.E.L.P., Kennedys of Massachusetts, Love and Lies, Marshall Chronicles, A Son's Promise, Story of the Beach Boys, Sunset Beat, Ted Koppel, To Be Free: National Literary Honors, and Wide World of Sports.
  - ABC stills, (1987 Dec) (Box 331, Folder 11)
    Dynasty, Head of the Class, Hotel, Mr. Belvedere, Not Quite Human, and others
  - ABC stills, (1987 Nov) (Box 331, Folder 10)
    The Charmings, Hooperman, Las Vegas: An All Star 75th Anniversary, MacGuyver, Ohara, Plaza Suite, Pursuit of Happiness, and Seasonal Differences.
  - ABC stills, (1987 Nov) (Box 331, Folder 9)
    Barbara Walters Special, A Christmas Memory, Dynasty, Eminent Domain, Good Morning America, Julie Andrews...The Sound of Christmas, Moonlighting, Mr. Belvedere, A Muppet Family Christmas, Sledge Hammer, The Three Kings, and others
  - ABC stills, (1987 Oct 13) (Box 331, Folder 5)
    Dynasty, Growing Pains, Head of the Class, Ohara, Sable, Sledge Hammer, Who's the Boss, and others
  - ABC stills, (1987 Oct 20 - 27) (Box 331, Folder 6)
    Head of the Class, The King of Love, Mr. Belvedere, The Pursuit of Happiness, Thirtysomething
  - ABC stills, (1987 Oct 6) (Box 331, Folder 8)
    Buck James, The Charmings, Perfect Strangers, Sledge Hammer, Spenser: For Hire, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1987 Sep 22) (Box 331, Folder 2)
    Best Defense, The Day My Kid Went Punk, Dynasty, Moonlighting, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Apr 12) (Box 331, Folder 12)
    China Beach, Chrysler Triple Crown, Richest Man in the World: The Story of Aristotle Onassis, Splash Too, Superstars and their Moms, With Peter Beard in Africa, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Apr 5) (Box 331, Folder 13)
    Heartbeat, Little Girl Lost, The Town Bully, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Feb 23) (Box 331, Folder 18)
    Broken Angel, Daddy Can't Read, Hotel, The Wonder Years, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Mar 22) (Box 331, Folder 15)
    60th Annual Academy Awards, Barbara Walters Special, Buck James, Family Man, Meet the Munceys, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Mar 29) (Box 331, Folder 14)
    Frank Nitti - The Enforcer, Just in Time, the Wonder Years, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Mar 8) (Box 331, Folder 17)
    Addicted to Love, Heartbeat, Supercarrier, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1987 Dec 22) (Box 332, Folder 5)
    Home and others.
  - ABC stills, (1987 Dec 29) (Box 332, Folder 4)
    XV Olympic Winter Games and others.
  - ABC stills, (1987 Feb 9) (Box 332, Folder 1)
    Perfect People, Probe, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Apr 12) (Box 332, Folder 6)
    The Bourne Identity, Home, Just the Ten of Us, Superstars and their Moms, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Apr 26) (Box 332, Folder 7)
    American Comedy Awards, Barbara Walters Special, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Jan 12) (Box 332, Folder 2)
    Earth*Star Voyager, Dolly, and others.
  - ABC stills, (1988 Jan 19) (Box 332, Folder 3)
    Elvis and Me, XV Olympic Winter Games, The Thorns, Weekend War, and others.
  - ABC stills, (ca. 1960s-1970s) (Box 332, Folder 10)
    The Thanksgiving Visitor and others.
  - ABC stills - 100th Tournament of Roses Parade, (1988 Dec 6) (Box 319, Folder 13)
  - ABC stills - ABC News, (1988-1990) (Box 319, Folder 14)
  - ABC stills - All My Children, (1989) (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - ABC stills - America's Funniest Home Videos, (1990) (Box 320, Folder 4)
  - ABC stills - Anything But Love, (1989-1990) (Box 320, Folder 5)
  - ABC stills - B.L. Stryker, (1989-1990) (Box 320, Folder 7)
  - ABC stills - Baby M, (1987 May-June) (Box 321, Folder 2)
  - ABC stills - Barbara Walters Special, (1988-1990) (Box 320, Folder 6)
  - ABC stills - Buck James, (1987) (Box 320, Folder 8)
  - ABC stills - Capital News, (1990 Mar-Apr) (Box 320, Folder 9)
  - ABC stills - Charmings (The), (1987 Sep) (Box 320, Folder 10)
  - ABC stills - Chicken Soup, (1989) (Box 320, Folder 11)
  - ABC stills - China Beach, (1988-1990) (Box 320, Folder 12)
  - ABC stills - Coach, (1989-1990) (Box 320, Folder 13)
  - ABC stills - Columbo, (1989-1990) (Box 320, Folder 14)
  - ABC stills - Date Rape, (1988 June-Aug) (Box 328, Folder 15)
  - ABC stills - Doogie Howser, M.D., (1989-1990) (Box 320, Folder 15)
  - ABC stills - Dynasty, (1986-1989) (Box 320, Folder 16)
  - ABC stills - Elvis, (1990 Jan-Feb) (Box 320, Folder 17)
  - ABC stills - Equal Justice, (1990 Mar-Apr) (Box 320, Folder 18)
  - ABC stills - Family Matters, (1989-1990) (Box 320, Folder 19)
  - ABC stills - Final Days (The), (1989 Oct 3) (Box 320, Folder 20)
  - ABC stills - Fine Romance (A), (1988-1989) (Box 320, Folder 21)
  - ABC stills - Free Spirit, (1989 May-Aug) (Box 320, Folder 22)
  - ABC stills - Full House, (1987-1990) (Box 320, Folder 23)
  - ABC stills - General Hospital, (1989 May-June) (Box 320, Folder 24)
  - ABC stills - General Hospital 25th Anniversary, (1988 Mar 8) (Box 331, Folder 16)
  - ABC stills - Gideon Oliver, (1989 Jan-May) (Box 320, Folder 25)
  - ABC stills - Good Morning America, (1988-1989) (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - ABC stills - Growing Pains, (1987-1990) (Box 320, Folder 2)
  - ABC stills - Hallmark Hall of Fame: The Shell Seekers, (1989 Nov 14) (Box 321, Folder 19)
  - ABC stills - Heartbeat, (1989 Jan 3) (Box 305, Folder 20)
  - ABC stills - Home, (1988 May, Nov) (Box 321, Folder 3)
  - ABC stills - Homeroom, (1989 May-Nov) (Box 321, Folder 4)
  - ABC stills - Hooperman, (1987-1989) (Box 321, Folder 5)
  - ABC stills - I Married Dora, (1987) (Box 321, Folder 6)
  - ABC stills - Just the Ten of Us, (1989 Apr-Oct) (Box 321, Folder 7)
  - ABC stills - Knightwatch, (1988 May-Nov) (Box 321, Folder 8)
  - ABC stills - Life Goes On, (1989-1990) (Box 321, Folder 9)
  - ABC stills - Living Dolls, (1989) (Box 321, Folder 10)
  - ABC stills - Love Among the Ruins, (ca. 1975) (Box 310, Folder 26)
    Found with Rock Hudson stills.
  - ABC stills - MacGyver, (1987-1989) (Box 321, Folder 11)
  - ABC stills - Max Headroom, (1987 May-Sep) (Box 321, Folder 12)
  - ABC stills - Men, (1989 Mar) (Box 321, Folder 13)
  - ABC stills - Mission Impossible, (1988, 1989) (Box 321, Folder 14)
  - ABC stills - Mr. Belvedere, (1987-1989) (Box 321, Folder 11)
  - ABC stills - Murphy's Law, (1987-1989) (Box 321, Folder 12)
  - ABC stills - Napoleon and Josephine: A Love Story, (1987 Oct) (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - ABC stills - North and South, (1988 Sep, 1989 Apr) (Box 321, Folder 13)
  - ABC stills - Once a Hero, (1987 Aug-Sep) (Box 321, Folder 14)
  - ABC stills - One Life to Live, (1987) (Box 305, Folder 18)
  - ABC stills - One Life to Live, (1988-1990) (Box 321, Folder 15)
  - ABC stills - Perfect Strangers, (1987-1990) (Box 321, Folder 16)
  - ABC stills - Preppie Murder (The), (1989) (Box 321, Folder 17)
  - ABC stills - Roseanne, (1988-1990) (Box 321, Folder 18)
  - ABC stills - Saturday Morning Childrens' Schedule, (1989-1990) (Box 328, Folder 7)
  - ABC stills - Slap Maxwell Story (The), (1987 Aug-Sep) (Box 328, Folder 1)
  - ABC stills - thirtysomething, (1987-1990) (Box 328, Folder 2)
  - ABC stills - Twin Peaks, (1990 Mar-May) (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - ABC stills - War and Remembrance, (1988 Oct, 1989 Apr) (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - ABC stills - Who's The Boss, (1987-1989) (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - ABC stills - Young Riders (The), (1989 Aug-Dec) (Box 328, Folder 6)
  - AIDS: Changing the Rules - stills, (undated) (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - American International Pictures stills, (c. 1973-1978) (Box 310, Folder 24)
    Coffy, Foxy Brown, and Scream Blacula Scream.
  - CBS stills, (1974 May-June) (Box 310, Folder 14)
  - CBS stills, (1978 Sep-Dec) (Box 310, Folder 13)
  - CBS stills, (1970s) (Box 332, Folder 11)
    M*A*S*H and others.
  - CBS stills, (ca. 1950s-1970s) (Box 332, Folder 19)
    Cinderella (1957), Barbra Streisand and Other Musical Instruments and others.
  - CBS stills - Ann Sothern Show, (undated) (Box 310, Folder 12)
  - CBS stills - Climax!: To Wake at Midnight headshot of Maria Riva, (undated) (Box 310, Folder 15)
  - Chiefs stills (KTVU), (undated) (Box 332, Folder 9)
  - Cinemax stills, (undated) (Box 310, Folder 18)
  - Film stills, (undated) (Box 332, Folder 13)
    The Outlaw, Robocop 2, and others.
  - HBO - Cyndi Lauper in Paris stills and press releases, (1987) (Box 310, Folder 19)
  - Hour Magazine - stills, (undated) (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - KQED stills, (undated) (Box 332, Folder 20)
  - Large Television Stills, (1959-1970) (Box 327, Folder 4)
    Stills from Bill Cosby Show (The), Bold Ones (The), Mothers-in-Law (The), Sinatra Show (The), and others.
  - NBC stills, (1974 May-Aug) (Box 310, Folder 22)
  - NBC stills, (1978 Sep-Nov) (Box 310, Folder 21)
  - NBC stills, (ca. 1970s) (Box 332, Folder 12)
  - NBC stills - Bob Hope Chrysler Theatre: Double Jeopardy, (undated) (Box 310, Folder 20)
  - Nelson Entertainment stills and press releases, (1986-1991) (Box 310, Folder 29)
    Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure and Misery.
  - Orion Pictures -stills, (1986 - 1987) (Box 331, Folder 3)
    Florida Straits and headshots of comedians including Roseanne Barr, Rodney Dangerfield, Jerry Seinfeld, and others.
  - Orion pictures stills and press releases (1 of 2), (1988-1991) (Box 310, Folder 27)
  - Orion pictures stills and press releases (2 of 2), (1988-1991) (Box 310, Folder 28)
    Brass, Mississippi Burning, and UHF.
  - PBS stills, (undated) (Box 332, Folder 18)
  - PBS stills - Upstairs Downstairs, (1987) (Box 310, Folder 11)
  - Personal snapshots, (undated) (Box 307, Folder 12)
  - Personal snapshots (2 items), (undated) (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Portraits, (undated) (Box 332, Folder 15)
    Fred Astaire, Annette Crosbie, Jon Cypher, Charles and Ray Eames
  - Radio - early photos, (undated) (Box 326, Folder 2)
    Photos of radio performers.
  - Robocop stills, (1987) (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Rock Hudson stills, (undated) (Box 310, Folder 25)
    Found with Love Among the Ruins stills.
  - Smithsonian News Service Sixty Years of Television: From a Flicker to a Glow stills and press release, (1988 Aug) (Box 310, Folder 17)
  - Spike Jones signed still, (undated) (Box 332, Folder 14)
  - TV stills - Special 1, (ca. 1950s-1960s) (Box 326, Folder 5)
    Includes stills from Andy Williams Show, Carol Burnett Show, Danny Kaye Show, Hollywood Palace, Peter Pan, Three Musketeers, Red Skelton Hour, and others.
  - TV stills - Special 2, (ca. 1950s-1970s) (Box 326, Folder 6)
    Includes stills from Alfred Hitchcock Hour, Cinderella, Ed Sullivan Show, Kraft Music Hall, Mike Douglas Show, Philco Television Playhouse, Texaco Star Theatre, and others.
  - TV stills - Special 3, (ca. 1950s-1970s) (Box 305, Folder 12)
    Includes stills from 77 Sunset Strip, All in the Family, Dinah Shore Chevy Show, Jack Benny Program, Laugh-In, Leave it to Beaver, Playhouse 60, Thin Man (The), and others.
  - Twentieth Century Fox stills, (c. 1978) (Box 310, Folder 23)
  - Unidentified negatives, (undated) (Box 305, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified photograph, (undated) (Box 305, Folder 11)
  - Westerns 1, (ca. 1950-1960) (Box 305, Folder 14)
    Bonanza, Gunsmoke, Overland Trail, Rawhide, Wanted - Dead or Alive, Wide Country, and other television Westerns.
  - Westerns 2, (ca. 1950-1970) (Box 305, Folder 15)
    Bonanza, The Cowboys, Gunsmoke, Have Gun Will Travel, Lancer, Laramie, Tombstone Territory, and other television Westerns.
  - WETA 26 stills and press releases, ([1988-1989]) (Box 310, Folder 16)
    Dateline Freedom and Savage Dream.
- Promotional Material, 1960s-1970s
  The series consists of press kits, print advertisements, preview invitations, and other promotional and souvenir objects pertaining to television programs and networks. Television program press kits may contain one or more of the following: detailed plots summaries, background information, lists of performers and information about their careers and off-camera lives, lists of production credits, information about sponsors and advertising agencies, and background information about the origin and development of programs. Some kits also mention production techniques used in creating the show, and some include favorable print reviews and productions stills. Network corporate press represent various networks' seasonal offerings of evening series, mini-series, late night shows, news and religious programs, and sports, etc. They include fact sheets describing the content of various shows, introducing performers and hosts, executive and production personnel, and sponsors and advertisers.
  The sereies is arranged in a loose alphabetical order.
  - Press kits (A-F), (various dates) (Box 300)
  - Press kits (F-L), (various dates) (Box 301)
  - Press kits (M-S), (various dates) (Box 302)
  - Press kits (S-Y), (various dates) (Box 303)
  - Press kits and advertising supplements, (ca. 1970-1980) (Box 327, Folder 3)
    Bronco Billy, Eleanor and Franklin: The White House Years, Flame Trees of Thika (The), Westinghouse Broadcasting Company.
  - Promotional items index, (undated) (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - 42nd Annual Academy Awards press kit, (ca. 1969-1970) (Box 307, Folder 5)
    With clippings, typescript pages, and notes.
  - A&E and Viewer's Choice advertisements, (c. 1987) (Box 332, Folder 16)
  - ABC TV Monday Night Football schedule, (1970) (Box 306, Folder 5)
  - Call Her Mom ABC Movie of the Week Alpha Rho Epsilon Fraternity Pin, (1972 Feb 2) (Box 319, Folder 7)
  - Call Her Mom promotional Alpha Rho Epsilon fraternity pin and note, (1972 Feb 2) (Box 319, Folder 9)
  - CBS Television Coronation Souvenir, (ca. 1953) (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Emmy Awards press releases, (1963, 1966) (Box 299, Folder 13)